<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book on 个人博客</title>
    <link>https://999338.xyz/categories/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book on 个人博客</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:39:55 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://999338.xyz/categories/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Death is inevitable, but whether one can maintain happiness until death is filled with uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://999338.xyz/posts/8b04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:39:55 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://999338.xyz/posts/8b04/</guid>
      <description>Reading Camus&amp;rsquo;s books always fills me with a sense of dread. His descriptions of absurdity and nihilism, along with his analysis of the meaning of life, often lead me to reflect deeply on my own existence. Every conscious person questions the meaning of their life. After all, if life has no meaning, why not end it now rather than go through the repetitive, meaningless days until death? It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder he said, &amp;ldquo;There is only one truly serious philosophical problem, and that is suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A person&#39;s life is made up of various sufferings|&#39;The Wisdom of Life&#39;</title>
      <link>https://999338.xyz/posts/8b03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:54:30 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://999338.xyz/posts/8b03/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;The Wisdom of Life&amp;rsquo; is a significant work by the famous German philosopher Arthur Schopenhauer. In this book, Schopenhauer explores the essence of human existence and the suffering that accompanies it. With his unique pessimistic outlook, he argues that life is fundamentally composed of various forms of suffering, and the pursuit of happiness is often in vain. Instead, he believes that we should focus on reducing suffering. This book is not only a profound reflection on life but also an in-depth analysis of human nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Factfulness&#39;by Hans Rosling: Understanding the Ten Cognitive Biases That Distort Our Perception of the World</title>
      <link>https://999338.xyz/posts/8b02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 12:13:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://999338.xyz/posts/8b02/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Factfulness&amp;rdquo; written by Swedish author Hans Rosling, is a widely acclaimed book aimed at helping readers understand the world more accurately through data and rational thinking. Rosling reveals ten common cognitive biases that distort our perception of the world and offers scientific data and examples to teach readers how to overcome these biases, ultimately fostering a more accurate and optimistic worldview.&#xA;The book begins by posing a series of simple questions to the reader, such as, &amp;ldquo;What percentage of girls in low-income countries finish primary school?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
