<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journey on 个人博客</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/journey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journey on 个人博客</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:50:19 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/journey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Guizhou Travel |A Paradise for Hikers and a Journey into Ethnic Diversity|Independent Travel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:50:19 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b11/</guid>
      <description>Guizhou Province has long been known for its &amp;ldquo;ethnic charm,&amp;rdquo; but few have truly ventured deep into southeastern Guizhou. Most people may recognize &amp;ldquo;Xijiang Qianhu Miao Village,&amp;rdquo; a highly renowned village. While Xijiang is indeed an impressive village, the over-commercialization of this tourist spot has somewhat diminished its former tranquility.&#xA;Today, let&amp;rsquo;s delve into Liping, Congjiang, and Rongjiang, to explore this colorful land and experience its true primitive and mysterious charm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Guide: The 10 Most Beautiful Border Cities in China! Experience Unique Ethnic Characteristics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 22:56:51 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b10/</guid>
      <description>The 10 Most Beautiful Border Cities in China! 1. Manzhouli (Inner Mongolia) - The Window of East Asia Located in the western part of Hulunbuir, Inner Mongolia, Manzhouli is a border city brimming with exotic charm. Bordering Russia to the north, this city blends the cultures of China, Russia, and Mongolia. Manzhouli&amp;rsquo;s architecture is unique, combining European, Chinese, and Russian styles, creating a bustling and picturesque atmosphere. Walking through the streets feels like stepping into a fairytale world full of mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Town Traveler&#39;s Guide|Top 50 Ancient City Worth Visiting in China</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 02:58:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b09/</guid>
      <description>China has over 2,800 ancient towns, distributed across the country. Many of these towns have a history of several hundred years, or even thousands of years. These ancient towns showcase a rich array of traditional architectural styles and unique folk cultures, reflecting the historical evolution of different regions and ethnic groups. Ancient towns are typically built by rivers, featuring distinctive natural landscapes and cultural environments. For example, Wuzhen and Zhouzhuang in the Jiangnan Water Towns are famous for their small bridges, flowing waters, and quaint houses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Allure of Beijing&#39;s Historic Hutongs|Tourist Attractions for Foreign Visitors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:38:55 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b08/</guid>
      <description>The Unique Charm of Beijing Hutongs As the capital of China, Beijing boasts a long and rich history, deeply embedded in its cultural heritage. Among the city&amp;rsquo;s most distinctive architectural forms, hutongs are not just narrow alleyways; they are vital spaces where the lifestyle and warmth of Beijing residents thrive. Exploring these hutongs offers visitors a glimpse into the historical ambiance of old Beijing while providing a deeper understanding of the city&amp;rsquo;s traditional culture and everyday life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Guide to Traveling in China|Top Travel Destinations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:08:15 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b07/</guid>
      <description>Travel isn&amp;rsquo;t just about showing others where you&amp;rsquo;ve been; it&amp;rsquo;s about transformation. Travel changes your perspective, widens your horizons, and helps you understand different ways of living. It fosters a broader mindset, allowing you to approach your own life with a refreshed attitude.&#xA;I. The Five Most Beautiful Lakes in China Qinghai Lake: The Inland Sea (Qinghai) – Best Season: All year round Kanas Lake: God&amp;rsquo;s Palette (Xinjiang) – Best Season: July to mid-September Namtso Lake: Where Gods Whisper (Tibet) – Best Season: July to September Heavenly Lake: Calm After the Storm (Jilin) – Best Season: July to September West Lake (Hangzhou) – Best Season: Year-round, each season has unique charm II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scenic Route: A Self-Driving Adventure on the 318 Sichuan|Tibet Line</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 23:59:30 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/8b06/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Sichuan-Tibet Highway 318 is a popular and classic self-driving route, favored by many adventurers. It typically refers to the section of National Highway 318 from Chengdu to Lhasa, covering about 2,000 kilometers. The southern Sichuan-Tibet line, located along the 30th parallel north, begins at Ya&amp;rsquo;an and diverges from National Highway 108. As it winds westward, it crosses Erlang Mountain and is renowned as &amp;ldquo;China&amp;rsquo;s Scenic Avenue.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;For a self-driving trip to Lhasa, it is recommended to start from Chengdu and pass through Luding—Kangding—Xinduqiao—Yajiang—Litang—Batang—Zuogong—Basu—Ranwu—Bomi—Motuo—Nyingchi, and finally reach Lhasa, the capital of Tibet.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
